Guide to the Douglas Menuez Photography Collection MSS.PHOTO.0451
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives
- Series 1. Silicon Valley Documentary, 1988-2002; 16.75 Linear feet
  - Subseries 2. Edits
    This subseries contains materials removed from the Silicon Valley Documentary series by Menuez and others for editorial purposes. Corresponding negatives to many, but not all contact sheets found in this subseries can be found in Series 3. Negatives (CLOSED to researchers).
    - Subsubseries 1. Reportage Selects
      This subsubseries includes the contents of a binder marked "Reportage Selects" and contains slides relating to Adobe, Farallon, TFI and Next, Inc..
      Doug Menuez formed Reportage in 1990 in order to build upon the successes of the Day in the Life series. The company is modeled upon Menuez's own practice of immersing himself in the corporate culture in order to capture images that can be used both for promotional and commercial purposes and photojournalistic ones. Reportage keeps photographers on month long retainers and asks them to spend a minimum of six months on the job. The photographer retains the right to use images for in-house purposes such as annual reports and fliers while Reportage itself lends editorial expertise and provides a photo-documentary clearing house.
      - Reportage selects, miscellaneous S-07, 35 mm. slides: black and white and color (Half-box 33, Folder 1)
      - Reportage selects, Adobe corp. S-07, 35 mm. slides: black and white (Half-box 33, Folder 2)
      - Reportage selects, Farallon S-07, 35 mm. slides: black and white (Half-box 33, Folder 3)
      - Reportage selects, TFI S-07, 35 mm. slides: black and white (Half-box 33, Folder 4)
      - Reportage selects, Next, Inc. [1 of 2] S-07, 35 mm. slides: black and white (Half-box 33, Folders 5-6)
    - Subsubseries 2. Silicon Valley Selects
      This subsubseries contains over 1,000 images selected by photo curator Karen Mullarkey. They match the images contained on CD in Series 4. Electronic Media.
      Please note: negatives labeled "Silicon Valley Selects" have been moved to Series 3. Negatives, but retain their original designation, for example, "Tech Selects 1."
      - Tech Selects 3, Apple Rocket Science 1996 S-07, 35 mm. slides: color (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Tech Selects 5, Sun Microsystems no. 1 S-07, 35 mm. slides: color (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Tech Selects 5, UC Pauson 1994 S-07, 35 mm. slides: color (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Tech Selects 6 [1 of 8] NetObjects 1994 S-07, 35 mm. slides: color (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Tech Selects 6 [2 of 8] Cray Computer 1994 S-07, Contact sheets: 28 x 22 cm. (Box 30, Folder 8)
        Contact sheets: 8414-8419
      - Tech Selects 6 [3 of 8] Cray Computer S-07, 35 mm slides: color (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Tech Selects 6 [4 of 8] Sun Microsystems S-07, 35 mm slides: color (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Tech Selects 6 [5 of 8] Adobe 1990 S-07, Contact sheets: 28 x 22 cm. (Box 30, Folder 11)
        Contact sheets: 34938-34949, 35071-35073, 03184, 03198
      - Tech Selects 6 [6 of 8] Adobe (Nextworld) 1991 Jan. S-07, Contact sheets: 28 x 22 cm. (Box 30, Folder 12)
        Contact sheet: 9718
      - Tech Selects 6 [7 of 8] Adobe S-07, 35 mm slides: color (Box 30, Folder 13)
        Includes photographs of art.
      - Tech Selects 6 [8 of 8] Earl Office (Nextworld) shot at Adobe 1991 Jan. S-07, Contact sheets: 22 x 28 cm.: black and white (Box 30, Folder 14)
        Contact sheets: 9180-9184
      - Tech Selects 6 [9 of 11] Next, Inc. n.d. S-07, 35 mm. slides: color. Yellow edit file. (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Tech Selects 6 [10 of 11] Next, Inc. n.d. S-07, Color prints (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Tech Selects 6 [11 of 11] Silicon Graphics, n.d. S-07, Color prints (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Tech Selects 7 [1 of 3] n.d. S-07, Adobe Systems, Kleiner, Perkins, Caulfield and Byers, Contact sheets: black and white (Box 31, Folder 4)
        Contains contact sheets 8477-8478, 8480-8486, 9166, 7401-7406, 7408-7411
      - Tech Selects 7 [2 of 3] n.d. S-07, Kleiner, Perkins, Caulfield and Byers, Contact sheets: black and white (Box 31, Folder 5)
        Contains contact sheets 7412-7425
      - Tech Selects 7 [3 of 3] n.d. S-07, Kleiner, Perkins, Caulfield and Byers, Contact sheets: black and white (Box 31, Folder 6)
        Contains contact sheets 74026, 74028-74043, 74045-74043
      - Tech Selects 8 [1 of 2] Farallon Tech Project A, n.d. S-07, Contact sheets: black and white (Box 31, Folder 7)
        Contains contact sheets 25520-25523, 26608-26610, 26612-26615, 26784, 27049-27060, 27842, 27844
      - Tech Selects 8 [2 of 2] Farallon Tech Project A, n.d. S-07, Contact sheets: black and white (Box 31, Folder 8)
        Contains contact sheets 27845-27852, 278771, 29463-29464, 29469, 39465-29467, 29471
      - Tech Selects 9 [1 of 3] Farallon Tech Project B, n.d. S-07, Contact sheets: black and white (Box 31, Folder 9)
        Contains contact sheets 03938, 04219, 8325, 03931, 8497, 8708, 8604, 8496, 8326, 03935, 8300, 8495, 8499, 8439, 8440, 8709
      - Tech Selects 9 [2 of 3] Farallon Tech Project B, n.d. S-07, Contact sheets: black and white (Box 31, Folder 10)
        Contains contact sheets 22960, 22962, 22067, 03942, 8829, 8830, 8782, 8781, 8770, 8771, 8766, 8765, 8764, 8121, 8122
      - Tech Selects 9 [3 of 3] Farallon Tech Project B, 1989-1990 S-07, Contact sheets: black and white (Box 31, Folder 11)
        Contains contact sheets B-03943, 8167, B-03941, 8828, 8827, 8788, 8787, 8785, 8772, 8786, 8784, 8783, 8432, 8433, 8129, 8127, 8128, 8065, 31527
      - Tech Selects 10 [1 of 2] IBM, Armonk & CEO, 1997 Dec., Contact sheets (color) (Box 32, Folder 1)
        Rolls 92-120
      - Tech Selects 10 [2 of 2] IBM, Armonk & CEO, 1997 Dec., Contact sheets (b/w) (Box 32, Folder 2)
        Rolls 1-7
      - Tech Selects 11 [1 of 8] Scott McNealy, Color slides (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Tech Selects 11 [2 of 8] Scott McNealy, Contact sheets and print (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Tech Selects 11 [3 of 8] Scott McNealy, Caption sheets (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Tech Selects 11 [4 of 8] John Doerr, 1986, Color slides (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Tech Selects 11 [5 of 8] John Doerr, Caption sheets (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Tech Selects 11 [6 of 8] John Sculley, 1989 Mar. - Apple Computer Inc., Fortune Magazine, Reportage, Money Magazine, USA Today, Color slides (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Tech Selects 11 [7 of 8] John Sculley, 1989 Mar., Color slides (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Tech Selects 11 [8 of 8] John Sculley, Caption sheets, clippings (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Tech Selects 12, Next, Inc. [1 of 8] S-07, 35 mm. slides: black and white (Box 32, Folder 11)
        Perot, Ross
      - Tech Selects 12, Apple Newton Project [2 of 8] S-07, 35 mm. slides: black and white (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Tech Selects 12, Next, Inc. [3 of 8] S-07, 35 mm. slides: black and white: photocopies (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - Tech Selects 12, Next, Inc. [3 of 8] S-07, 35 mm. slides: black and white: photocopies (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - Tech Selects 12, Adobe [5 of 8] 1987-1992 S-07, 35 mm. slides: black and white (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - Tech Selects 12, DuPont Recycling Program [6 of 8] S-07, 35 mm. slides: black and white (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - Tech Selects 12, Technology Fund [7 of 8] S-07, 35 mm. slides: black and white (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - Tech Selects 12, Miscellaneous [8 of 8] S-07, 35 mm. slides: black and white (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Series 3. Negatives, 5.25 Linear feet
  This series consists of negatives corresponding to many, but not all, contact sheets found in Series 1. Silicon Valley Documentary.
  Conditions Governing Access note
  Series 3, Negatives, is CLOSED except to staff for duplication purposes. Researchers should refer to the corresponding contact sheets in Series 1. To request copies of images, please refer to job and roll number.
  - Adobe 1988, binder no. 1 [1 of 7], 1988 August; S-01 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Negatives: rolls: 15294-16844
  - Adobe 1988, binder no. 1 [2 of 7], 1988 August; S-01 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Negatives: rolls: 16845-18150
  - Adobe 1988, binder no. 1 [3 of 7], 1988 September; S-01 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Negatives: rolls: 01707-01709, 19404-19409
  - Adobe 1988, binder no. 1 [4 of 7], 1988 September; S-01 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Negatives: rolls: 19410-19416
  - Adobe 1988, binder no. 1 [5 of 7], 1988 October; S-01 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Negatives: rolls: 04157-04161, 02671-02672
  - Adobe 1988, binder no. 1 [6 of 7], 1988 December; S-01 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Negatives: rolls: 08345, 08437-08441, 08979-08988
  - Adobe 1988, binder no. 1 [7 of 7], 1988 December; S-01 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Negatives: rolls: 09149-09156, 09229-09232
  - Adobe no. 1, 1989 [1 of 8], 1989 January; S-01 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Negatives: rolls: 11577-11581
  - Adobe no. 1, 1989 [2 of 8], 1989 March; S-01 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Negatives: rolls: 16770. Note: rolls 15340-15342, 16769 missing.
  - Adobe no. 1, 1989 [3 of 8], 1989 June; S-01 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Negatives: rolls: 26786-26787, 27138-27139, 27144-27146
  - Adobe no. 1, 1989 [4 of 8], 1989 July; S-01 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Negatives: rolls: 27863-27872
  - Adobe no. 1, 1989 [5 of 8], 1989 August; S-01 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Negatives: roll: 32405
  - Adobe no. 1, 1989 [6 of 8], 1989 October; S-01 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Negatives: rolls: 0035-0041
  - Adobe no. 1, 1989 [7 of 8], 1989 December 12; S-01 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Negatives: rolls: 8073-8078
  - Adobe no. 1, 1989 [8 of 8], 1989 December 12; S-01 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Negatives: rolls: 8087-8098
  - Adobe color, 1990 [1 of 3], 1989 December 12; S-01 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Negatives: rolls: 1000-1011
  - Adobe color, 1990 [2 of 3], 1989 December 12; S-01 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Negatives: rolls: 42264-42267, 42277, 42423
  - Adobe color, 1990 [3 of 3], 1989 December 12; S-01 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Negatives: rolls: 42339-42348a
  - Adobe Annual No. 1, 1990 [1 of 3], 1989 December 12; S-01 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Negatives: rolls: 8941-8958
  - Adobe Annual No. 1, 1990 [2 of 3], 1989 December 12; S-01 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Negatives: rolls: 8975, 9004-9020
  - Adobe Annual No. 1, 1990 [3 of 3], 1989 December 12; S-01 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Negatives: rolls: 9021-9038
  - Adobe Annual No. 2, 1990 [1 of 2], 1989 December 12; S-01 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Negatives: rolls: 9043-9059, 9062-9065, 9117-9123
  - Adobe Annual No. 2, 1990 [2 of 2], 1989 December 12; S-01 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Negatives: rolls: 9124-9129, 63476-63485, 63512-63519
  - Adobe Annual, No. 3, 1990; S-01 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Negatives: rolls: 8217-8219, 8472-8476, 8551-8558, 8682-8686, 8940
  - Adobe 1991 [1 of 3], S-01 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Negatives: rolls: 9506-9507, 9518-9530, 9440-9443, 9633-9640
  - Adobe 1991 [2 of 3], S-01 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Negatives: rolls: 9641-9651, 68953-68954, 68956-68961, 71122-71130
  - Adobe 1991 [3 of 3], S-01 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Negatives: rolls: 71131, 72184-72187, 72189, 72627-72636
  - Adobe 1991 no. 2, S-01 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Negatives: rolls: 73029, 73031-73036. Includes Adobe Halloween (1991 Oct.)
  - Adobe 1992, no. 1 [1 of 2], S-01 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Negatives: rolls: 78411-78430, 8138-8143
  - Adobe 1992, no. 1 [2 of 2], S-01 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Negatives: rolls: 8144-8151, 81801-81821, 81823-81824
  - Adobe 1994, no. 1, 1994 July 8; S-01 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Negatives: rolls: 1-18.
  - Adobe 1995 (Seattle), S-01 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Negatives: rolls: 07393-07399
  - Apple 1990-1991, no. 1 [1 of 3], S-03 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Negatives: rolls: 8578-8587
  - Apple 1990-1991, no. 1 [2 of 3], S-03 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Negatives: rolls: 88588-8592, 8842-8865
  - Apple 1990-1991, no. 1 [3 of 3], S-03 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Negatives: rolls: 8588-8592, 8842-8865
  - Apple 1990-1991, no. 1 [3 of 3], S-03 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Negatives: rolls: 8866-8874, 64877-64899
  - Apple 1992, no. 1 [1 of 2], S-03 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Negatives: rolls: 78431-78456. Apple "Back to School."
  - Apple 1992, no. 1 [2 of 2], S-03 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Negatives: rolls: 776724-76742, 8427-8428
  - Apple Super-Mac, 1993, no. 1, S-03 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Negatives: rolls: 5401-5406, 63431, 63441, 63443, 63448, 63453a
  - Apple Blue Print no. 1 [1 of 3], 1994; S-03 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Negatives: rolls: 99212-99225, 99227-99240
  - Apple Blue Print no. 1 [2 of 3], 1994; S-03 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Negatives: rolls: 99241-99265
  - Apple Blue Print no. 1 [3 of 3], 1994; S-03 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Negatives: rolls: 99266-99280
  - Apple Blue Print no. 2 [1 of 2], 1994; S-03 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Negatives: rolls: 99532-99538, 99791-99793
  - Apple Blue Print no. 2 [2 of 2], 1994; S-03 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Negatives: rolls: 98911-98924, 71086-71088
  - Apple Computer 1996, no. 1, S-03 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Negatives: rolls: 00257-00274, 00711, 45619, 45645, 45646, 45647, 45648
  - Apple, the New Mac, 1997 July; S-03 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Negatives: rolls: 1-47
  - Apple, no. 1, 1991 January; S-03 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Negatives: rolls: 64942-64959
  - Apple education brochure [1 of 2], 1989; S-03 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Negatives: rolls: 15473-15487, 15488-15489, 15805-15818
  - Apple education brochure [2 of 2], 1989; S-03 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Negatives: rolls: 16042-16056
  - Newton 1992, no. 1, S-04, S-05 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Negatives: rolls: 77931-77943, 78111-78128, 78532-78552
  - Newton 1992, no. 2 [1 of 2], S-04, S-05 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Negatives: rolls: 79091-79130
  - Newton 1992, no. 2 [2 of 2], S-04, S-05 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Negatives: rolls: 79131-79160
  - Newton 1992, no. 3 [1 of 2], S-04, S-05 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Negatives: rolls: 64580-64581, 80170, 81321-81328, 60004, 10-17, 25-32, 88473-88481a, 88483, 40-45
  - Newton 1992, no. 3 [2 of 2], S-04, S-05 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Negatives: rolls: 8131-8135, 8273-8281, 8286-8299, 70145, 79096, 79777
  - Newton 1992, no. 4, S-04, S-05 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Negatives: rolls: 8380-8402, 8424-8426, 62583-62591
  - Newton 1992, no. 5, S-04, S-05 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Negatives: rolls: 9000, 9003, 8247-8255y, 8260-8272, 8276, 8278, 8300-8309, 8358-8379
  - Newton 1993, no. 1 [1 of 2], S-04, S-05 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Negatives: rolls: 63857-63525, 63427-63430, 63432-63435, 63437-63440, 63442, 63442, 63444-63446, 63449-63452, 63454-63458, 68809
  - Newton 1993, no. 1 [2 of 2], S-04, S-05 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Negatives: rolls: 63527-63542, 69231-69238, 69320-69330, 69314-69319
  - Newton 1993, no. 2 [1 of 2], S-04, S-05 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Negatives: rolls: 63846-66852, 67076-67077, 66973-66978, 64276-64278, 64280-64300
  - Newton 1993, no. 2 [2 of 2], S-04, S-05 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Negatives: rolls: 64301-64320, 64436-64439
  - Newton 1993, no. 3 [1 of 2], S-04, S-05 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Negatives: rolls: 644495-64517, 64797-64812
  - Newton 1993, no. 3 [2 of 2], S-04, S-05 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Negatives: rolls: 65259-65260, 65679-65683, 70158-70162, 70283-70293, 64507, 64510, 64512, 64513
  - Newton 1993, no. 4 [1 of 2], S-04, S-05 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Negatives: rolls: 70136-70155, 70620-70631
  - Newton 1993, no. 4 [2 of 2], S-04, S-05 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Negatives: rolls: 70675, 70893-70897, 71106, 71391, 71449-71459, 71986, 80437-80451
  - Newton 1993, no. 5, S-04, S-05 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Negatives: rolls: 82206, 82332-82375, 84426-84429
  - Newton 1993, no. 6 [1 of 2], S-04, S-05 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Negatives: rolls: 80528-80541, 80699-80707, 81178-81181
  - Newton 1993, no. 6 [2 of 2], S-04, S-05 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Negatives: rolls: 81793-81825
  - Newton Selects [1 of 5], 1993; S-04, S-05 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Newton Selects [2 of 5], 1993; S-04, S-05 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Newton Selects [3 of 5], 1993; S-04, S-05 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Newton Selects [4 of 5], 1993; S-04, S-05 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Newton Selects [5 of 5], 1993; S-04, S-05 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Newton copy negatives [1 of 2], S-04, S-05 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Newton copy negatives [2 of 2], S-04, S-05 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Kleiner Perkins, Caulfield and Byers, no. 1, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Negatives: rolls: 08245, 08246, 08248, 06649-06652, 06655, 06656, 07419-07420, 07419-07420, 07567-07575
  - Kleiner Perkins, Caulfield and Byers, no. 2 [1 of 3], 1992 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Negatives: rolls: 74672-74675, 74677-74686, 06333-06337
  - Kleiner Perkins, Caulfield and Byers, no. 2 [2 of 3], 1992 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Negatives: rolls: 06338-06348, 66959-06964
  - Kleiner Perkins, Caulfield and Byers, no. 2 [3 of 3], 1992 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Negatives: rolls: 06965-06969, 07245-07251, 76817-76821, 62752-62753, 77020, 62749-62751, 77016-77018
  - Kleiner Perkins, Caulfield and Byers 1995 June-1995 Nov., no. 1 [1 of 2] (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Negatives: rolls: X-97744, 02635-02646, 02648-02666
  - Kleiner Perkins, Caulfield and Byers 1995 June-1995 Nov., no. 1 [2 of 2] (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Negatives: rolls: 02667-02669, 02677-02678, 08379-08390, 10058-10063, 10249-10257, 4998
  - Kleiner Perkins, Caulfield and Byers, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Negatives: rolls: 43788-43793, 43827-43829, ends, 43988-43991
  - Kleiner Perkins, Caulfield and Byers, President Clinton dinner, no. 2, 1996 September (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Negatives: rolls: 46561-45664, 46597-46600, 46612-46616, ends, 1-3
    Clinton, Bill, 1946-
  - Next 1, Sonoma Mission Inn Retreat, 1986 September 8 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Negatives: rolls: 0767-0771
  - Next, Inc. 1, 1986 October (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Negatives: rolls: 0110-0118
  - Next, Inc. 1, 1986 November (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Negatives: rolls: 0673-0679
  - Next, Inc. 1, 1986 December (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Negatives: rolls: 1000-1004
  - Next, Inc. 1, Palo Alto Retreat, 1987 January (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Negatives: rolls: 0780-0785
  - Next, Inc. 1, 1987 February (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Negatives: rolls: 2100, 61169
  - Next, Inc. 1, 1987 March (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Negatives: rolls: 0839-0843, 188644-188646, 6874
  - Next, Inc. 1, 1987 May (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Negatives: rolls: 011779-011782, 62486-62488
  - Next, Inc. 1, Company picnic, 1987 August (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Negatives: rolls: 3039-3045
  - Next, Inc. 1, 1987 September (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Negatives: rolls: 23690-23702
  - Next, Inc. 1, Chaminade retreat, 1987 October (Box 8, Folder 11)
    Negatives: rolls: 61192
  - Next, Inc. 1, 1987 November (Box 8, Folder 12)
    Negatives: rolls: 24560-24564
  - Next, Inc. 1, 1987 December (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Negatives: rolls: 25651
  - Next, Inc. 2 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    Negatives: rolls: 01691-01692
  - Next, Inc. 2, 1988 January (Box 8, Folder 15)
    Negatives: rolls: 090178-090181
  - Next, Inc. 2, 1988 March (Box 8, Folder 16)
    Negatives: rolls: 31788-31790
  - Next, Inc. 2, 1988 May (Box 8, Folder 17)
    Negatives: rolls: 73830-73835
  - Next, Inc. 2, Chaminade retreat, 1988 June (Box 8, Folder 18)
    Negatives: rolls: 07110-07115
  - Next, Inc. 2, 1988 July (Box 8, Folder 19)
    Negatives: rolls: 15288-15293
  - Next, Inc. 2, 1988 September - October (Box 8, Folder 20)
    Negatives: rolls: 012101215, 01240, 02667-02670, 04070-04072. Note: no corresponding contact sheet.
  - Next, Inc. 2, Education conference at the National Air and Space Museum (Washington, D.C.), 1988 October (Box 8, Folder 21)
    Negatives: rolls: 05169-05181, 05195-05198
  - Next, Inc. 2, Ryan Connel, 1988 November (Box 8, Folder 22)
    Negatives: rolls: 06392-06393. Note: no corresponding contact sheets.
  - Next, Inc. 2, Christmas Party, 1988 December (Box 8, Folder 23)
    Negatives: rolls: 09537-09540
  - Next, Inc. 3, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    Negatives: rolls: 12465-12469
  - Next, Inc. 3, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    Negatives: rolls: 25663-25667
  - Next, Inc. 3, Next factory, 1990 January 8-9 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    Negatives: rolls: 8178, 8184, 8204, 8174 Note: No corresponding contact sheets.
  - Next, Inc. 4, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    Negatives: rolls: 8211-8215, 8220, 8234-8236, 8173, 8175-8183, 8185-8203 Note: No corresponding contact sheets.
  - Next, Inc. 4, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    Negatives: rolls: 8205-8210, 8221-8233, 8216
  - Next, Inc. 4, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    Negatives: rolls: 68809-68827, 68837-68842, 68873-68875
  - Tech Selects 1 [1 of 4] Adobe 1988, S-07; 35 mm negatives: black and white (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Negatives: rolls: 15294, 15807, 15803, 16844, 16846, 16847, 16849, 16928, 16928?, 01709, 19404, 19405, 19407, 19412, 19414, 19415, 19416, 04158, 04158, 04159, 04160, 04160, 04161, 02673, 08345, 08439, 08979, 08980, 08982, 08983, 08984, 08985, 08986, 08987, 09150, 09154, 09155
  - Tech Selects 1 [2 of 4] Adobe 1989, S-07; 35 mm negatives: black and white (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Negatives: rolls: 11577-11581, 16770, 26786, 26787, 27138, 27139, 27144, 27863-27866, 27870, 27871, 32405, 0035-0041, 8073-8077, 8087-8093, 8095, 8097, 8098
  - Tech Selects 1 [3 of 4] Adobe Annual, 1990; S-07; 35 mm negatives: black and white (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Negatives: rolls: 8945,-8949, 8954, 9004, 9005, 9008-9009, 9012, 9014, 9015, 9017, 9019, 9023, 9026, 9030, 9031, 9033, 9044, 9046-9048, 9052-9053, 9059, 9063, 9117, 9118, 9120, 9122, 9123, 9126, 9127, 63476, 63478, 63482, 63512, 63515, 63516
  - Tech Selects 1 [4 of 4] Adobe Annual, 1990; S-07; 35 mm negatives: black and white (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Negatives: rolls: 8218, 8219, 8551, 8553, 8554, 8556, 8558, 8683, 8684, 8684, 8940
  - Tech Selects 2 [1 of 11] Adobe color 1990, S-07; 35 mm negatives: color (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Negatives: rolls: 1001-1005, 1010, 42423, 42342, 42344, 42346, 42348
  - Tech Selects 2 [2 of 11] Adobe, 1990 July; S-07; 35 mm negatives: black and white (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Negatives: rolls: 8478, 8485
  - Tech Selects 2 [3 of 11] Adobe, 1991; S-07; 35 mm negatives: black and white (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Negatives: rolls: 9523, 9529, 9633, 9636, 9637, 9640-9642, 9647-9650, 71124, 71126-71129, 72185-42186, 72189, 72627, 72634, 72635
  - Tech Selects 2 [4 of 11] Adobe, 1991; S-07; 35 mm negatives: black and white (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Negatives: rolls: 73029, 73031-73034
  - Tech Selects 2 [5 of 11] Adobe, 1992; S-07; 35 mm negatives: black and white (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Negatives: rolls: 8138, 8140, 8142, 8143, 8145,-8150, 78412, 78413, 78418, 78419, 78424-78430, 81802, 81805-81807, 81809, 81810, 81812
  - Tech Selects 2 [6 of 11] Adobe, 1994; S-07; 35 mm negatives: black and white (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Negatives: rolls: 1, 3, 5, 9, 17, 18
  - Tech Selects 2 [7 of 11] Adobe Seattle, 1995 October; S-07; 35 mm negatives: black and white (Box 9, Folder 11)
    Negatives: rolls: 07395, 07396, 07398, 07399
  - Tech Selects 2 [8 of 11] Apple, 1990-1991; S-07; 35 mm negatives: black and white (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Unnumbered negative sheets.
  - Tech Selects 2 [9 of 11] Apple Super Mac, 1993; S-07; 35 mm negatives: color (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Negatives: rolls: 5401, 5402, 5404, 5406, 63431, 63441, 63453
  - Tech Selects 2 [10 of 11] Apple Blueprint, 1994; S-07; 35 mm negatives: black and white (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Negatives: rolls: 99227, 99228, 99231, 99232, 99236, 99267, 99223, 99244, 99247, 99249, 99257, 99244, 99223, 99246
  - Tech Selects 2 [11 of 11] Apple Blueprint book 2, 1994; S-07; 35 mm negatives: black and white (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Tech Selects 3 [1 of 9] Apple Computer, 1996 July; S-07; 35 mm negatives: black and white (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Negatives: rolls: 00257-00260, 00262, 00265-00270, 00272, 00274, 00711, 45645, 45620, 45646
  - Tech Selects 3 [2 of 9] Farallon, 1989 January - November; S-07; 35 mm negatives: black and white (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Negatives: rolls: 16150-16152, 16154, 16155, 17661-17663, 22134, 22136, 22959, 23918, 31519, 31520, 21522, 31525, 31526, 17662-17663, 17665, 17666, 22063, 22064, 22044, 22066, 22959, 22134, 19710